Tenchi Bridge
(サイ)天地橋周辺に人の気配はない。
I don't sense the presence of
anyone around the Tenchi Bridge...
(ヤマト)暁の待ち伏せ
という線は消えたか。
I guess that means there won't
be any Akatsuki ambush, huh...?
よし それでは
予定どおり行動しよう。
All right! Then let's proceed
as planned.
Right!
(ナルト)おう！
ナルト すまないが これを持って➡
Naruto.
Could you take this and
hold it towards me?
ボクのほうへ向けてくれないか？
(ヤマト)よし いいぞ
こっちに向けてくれ。
All right, that's good.
Hold it towards me.
Wood Style: Transformation!
木遁変化！
どうだ？ うまくいったか？
So? Did it turn out okay?
(サクラ)はい！ どこから見ても
サソリの傀儡 ヒルコそのものです。
Yes, it did!
You look like Sasori's puppet
Hiruko in every way.
では 声の調子を
合わせておきたい。
Now I want to adjust the voice.
Let me know when it sounds right.
いいところで ストップをかけてくれ。
はい。
Yes, sir!
あっあっ あぁ～…。
ああぁ～…。
Oh!
That's it. That's the voice.
あっ それそれ！ そんな声です。
それじゃあ これより
作戦に入るからね。
Then we're going to start
the operation, okay?
Your tone is too polite.
口調が丁寧すぎます。
もっと こう 乱暴っていうか➡
You need to sound more violent
or surly or something...
ぶっきらぼうっていうか…。
あぁ そうだったね。
Oh...That's right.
人を待つのも待たせるのも
嫌いな➡
I'm irritable, and hate waiting
and being kept waiting.
短気な性格だ。
Okay, we're starting the operation!
では 今から作戦に入るぞ！
ウハハハッ！ そうそう
そんな感じだったってばよ。
Right-right.
That's what he was like!
(ヤマト)では
相手も警戒しているはず。
Okay, our opponent should be
on the alert. We'll split up now!
ここからは別行動だ。
だが チームワーク厳守だ。
Observe teamwork at all times!
Especially you, Naruto!
特にナルト
合図前に飛び出すんじゃねえぞ。
Don't be jumping out before
I give the signal!
行くぞ！
Let's go!
《ヤマト : さて 行くか》
Okay...Time to go.
《サクラ : 風が強い… これなら！》
The wind's strong. This should...
《サクラちゃん…》
Sakura...
《サクラ : うん… ここならいい》
Yeah, this spot should be okay.
《サクラ : そろそろ正午…》
It's almost noon...
まだかよ!? スパイ野郎は…。
That spy jerk...isn't he here yet?
(サイ)アイツか…。
Is that him?
The Tenchi Bridge
来たってばよ。
Here he comes.
((サソリ : 草隠れの里にある
天地橋に➡
At midday in ten days,
go to the Tenchi Bridge
十日後の真昼に行け。
located in
the Village Hidden in the Grass!
大蛇丸の部下に オレのスパイがいる。
I've got a spy working as one
of Orochimaru's subordinates...
(そこで ソイツと落ち合う…
ことになって…))
I was supposed to
rendezvous...with him...there...
《ヤマト : アイツか…》
That's him, huh...?
《サクラ : ヤマト隊長…
うまくやってよ》
Captain Yamato...
I hope you do okay...
お久しぶりです… サソリ様。
It's been a long time, Lord Sasori.
《コイツは…》
He's...
(カブト)５年ぶりですね。
It's been five years, hasn't it?
《薬師 カブト…》
Kabuto Yakushi...
尾行は？
Were you followed...?
大丈夫です。
We're okay...
(ヤマト)調子はどうだ？
How're you doing?
(カブト)サソリ様の術が解け➡
I've still got the strange sensation...
自分が何者であるか
思い出したときの➡
from when I remembered who I was
after your Jutsu broke...
奇妙な気分が残ってて…。
まだ少し 頭が重いです。
I still feel heavy-headed...
また アイツか！
Him again...?!
まさか 暁のスパイが
カブトだったなんて…。
Who would've thought...
the Akatsuki spy was Kabuto.
(ヤマト)いくつか質問する。
I've got some questions for you.
(カブト)時間がありませんから
手短にお願いします。
I don't have much time,
so please keep it short.
大蛇丸の目を盗んで
ここまで来るのも➡
I risked my life to get here
without Orochimaru finding out.
命がけですから。
アジトの場所と➡
I want information about
うちは サスケについての情報をくれ。
the location of his hideout
and Sasuke.
アジトは いくつもあって➡
There are several hideouts.
居場所がバレぬよう 一週単位で➡
We move to
a different hideout each week
各所を転々と移動しています。
so as not to get discovered.
(カブト)それは もちろん
音隠れの里以外の➡
Of course there are hideouts,
not just in the Village Hidden
in the Sound, but in other lands as well.
他国にもあって 大蛇丸のスパイが
入り込んで 手引きしています。
Spies for Orochimaru infiltrate
and act as informers.
ただ 移動手段もまちまちで
そう簡単には…。
But there are all sorts of
means of transport,
so they're not easily tracked...
(ヤマト)今は？
Where is it now?
今は 北の湖の小島の
アジトに潜伏していて➡
We're now in a hideout
on a small island on
a lake to the north.
あと 三日で移動します。
We'll be moving again in three days.
(カブト)そこに うちは サスケもいます。
Sasuke Uchiha is there as well.
風の音が強くって
全然 聞き取れねえってばよ。
The sound of the wind is so loud
I can't hear anything.
(サクラ)バカね！ だからこそ
逆に 私たちも➡
You idiot! That's why we were
able to get this close.
ここまで近寄れるんじゃない。
The wind blows away the noise and
smell, so we can sit here unnoticed.
音も匂いも
風が飛ばしてくれるから➡
気づかれないのよ！
ところで…。
By the way...
なんだ… 野ウサギか…。
Oh...it's just a wild rabbit.
ところで… サソリ様より
命ぜられていた➡
By the way...
About what you ordered me to do,
Lord Sasori...
例の件ですが…。
《やばいな… 今のうちに
聞き出しておきたいことが➡
Uh oh...
I still had a few more things
I wanted to ask him
もう少しあったが…➡
while I had the chance, but...
これ以上会話を続けると
ボロが出る…》
I'll be discovered if the conversation
continues any further...
(カブト)大蛇丸は転生後も➡
Even after his reincarnation,
使い捨てた遺体の細胞標本に
術でプロテクトをかけていて➡
Orochimaru uses a Jutsu
to apply a protector
to the cellular specimens
from his discarded body...
その細胞データを 解析することは
ボクには できませんでした。
And therefore I was unable
to analyze the cellular data.
そうか…。
I see...
な～にしてんだってばよ！
What's he doing?!
He should just grab him!
さっさと 捕らえりゃ
いいじゃねえか！
相手は あのカブトよ！
His opponent is Kabuto.
慎重すぎるくらいで
ちょうどいいのよ。
Being overly cautious is just fine.
It's all over if he gets away, right?
もし 取り逃がしでもしたら
おしまいでしょ？
(サイ)でも…➡
But...
あまり慎重になりすぎて
怪しまれたら➡
The spy could get suspicious
if he's too cautious...
拘束するタイミングを失うよ。
and the timing to capture him
will get thrown off.
それは… ヤマト隊長を
信じるしかないわ。
We'll...
just have to believe in
Captain Yamato about that...
(カブト)では すぐにでも
例のものを渡してください。
Now, please hand over
the item in question immediately.
ボクも これ以上
ゆっくりしていられません。
I can't be hanging around here
any longer.
(カブト)ここで あなたと
こうしていることが バレたら➡
If it's discovered that I'm here
with you like this...
ボクは 殺されてしまう…。
I'll be killed.
わかった…。
Okay...
《限界だな… もう ここらへんで
やるしかない！》
I can't hold out any longer...
I just have to capture him
here and now!
(大蛇丸)おもしろそうな話ね。
That conversation sounds interesting.
(大蛇丸)私も会話に
混ぜてもらえるかしら？
Would you guys let me
join in as well?
《あっ！ つけられてたか！》
He was followed!
大蛇丸！
あ…。
Orochimaru!
《あれが…》
That's...?
サソリ様がクナイを出さなければ➡
If you hadn't pulled out
a Kunai Knife,
気づかずに
逃げ遅れるところでした。
I wouldn't have been able
to get away before I noticed.
《うまい具合に勘違い
してくれたようだな…➡
It looks like he's
misunderstood nicely...
とりあえずは バレずに済んだか…。
I guess I still haven't been
discovered for now...
しかし 大蛇丸が
出てきたとなると…➡
But...now that Orochimaru
has shown up...
さて… どうする？》
What should I do?
その装束 懐かしいわね サソリ…。
That outfit...sure takes me back...
Sasori...
カブトをつけてきたのか？
Did you follow Kabuto?
なに 少し礼を
言おうと思ってね…。
Oh... I just thought I'd thank you.
あなたが送り込んでくれたこの子
すごく重宝したわ…。
This kid you sent to me...
has come in very handy.
(大蛇丸)新しい術を
一つ開発するのに必要な➡
The number of human subjects
necessary for the development
of one new Jutsu is over a hundred...
人体実験の数は100体以上…。
(大蛇丸)使い終わった実験体も
この子の医療忍術のおかげで➡
Thanks to this kid's Medical Ninjutsu,
I've been able to reuse
test subjects several times.
何度も
使いまわすことが出来たわ…。
実験体も
なかなか不足しててね…。
There's been a great shortage
of them, you see...
どうすんだってばよ!?
What do we do?!
(サクラ)隊長の指示があるまでは
待機するしかないわ。
We just have to stand by until
the Captain gives us instructions.
《恐らく ボク１人で
大蛇丸の相手をするのはムリだ…。
It would probably be
impossible for me
to take on Orochimaru alone...
カブトと協力して
大蛇丸を止めるにしても…。
But even if I can stop Orochimaru
by working together with Kabuto...
戦い方で ボクがサソリでないことは
すぐ バレてしまう…。
he'll find out immediately that
I'm not Sasori by my fighting style...
かといって ３人を呼べば…。
Even so, if I call those three...
then Kabuto will find out
who I am
今度は カブトにこちらの素性がバレて
拘束は厄介になる…。
and it will become difficult
to capture him...
すぐに ３人を呼んで
どちらも倒すか➡
Either I have to immediately call
the three and defeat both of them...
それとも 呼ばずに
このままひくか…。
or retreat as is without calling them...
その どちらかだが…》
I'll have to do one or the other...
《バレたのか… いや 違うな…。
Have I been discovered?
No... that's not it...
これは どういうことだ…!?》
What's the meaning of this?!
潜影多蛇手！
Multiple Striking Shadow Snake!
(大蛇丸)これは…
木遁忍術での変わり身…。
This is a Substitution created
with the Wood Style Ninjutsu...
あなた… まさか…。
You... could it be...?
大蛇丸様。
コイツが サソリの本体ですか？
Lord Orochimaru.
Is this Sasori's real body?
いいえ… 違うわ…。
No... It isn't...
カブト…。
お前 サソリの部下だったくせに➡
Kabuto... you didn't know
his real face
本当の顔も知らないでいたの？
even though you were
his subordinate?
いつも傀儡の中に隠れてる➡
He was a broody guy
who always stayed hidden
陰気なヤツでしたからね…。
inside his puppets, after all...
どういうことだ…？
What's the meaning of this...?!
(ヤマト)カブト…！
お前は暁のスパイのはず…！
Kabuto... you were supposed
to be an Akatsuki spy...
(ヤマト)サソリに ずっと術をかけらて
いたんじゃなかったのか!?
Weren't you caught in one
of Sasori's Jutsu all this time?!
そんな術 とっくに大蛇丸様が
解いてくれた。
Lord Orochimaru...broke that Jutsu
for me ages ago...
(ヤマト)サソリの術に
かかったままのフリをして➡
I can't believe you went
to the other side
寝返って いたとはな…！
pretending to be caught
in one of Sasori's Jutsu...
大蛇丸の術に落ちたか…！
Did you get caught in one
of Orochimaru's Jutsu...?
いや 違うな…。
No... that's not it.
ボクはただ 大蛇丸様のお考えに
共感しただけさ。
I just empathize with
Lord Orochimaru's ideas.
(カブト)ところで アンタは誰だ？
By the way, who are you?
サソリを 始末する予定だったのに
とんだ手違いだよ。
The plan was to take
care of Sasori.
But something has gone
quite wrong.
(大蛇丸)カブト… この子のことは
後で説明してあげるわ。
Kabuto... I'll tell you
about this kid later...
(大蛇丸)それより…
後ろの 子ネズミ３匹も➡
More importantly...
Why don't you call the three
little mice behind you over here?
ここへ 呼んだらどう…？
《すべて
お見通しってわけか…》
So he's seen through
everything, huh...?
《サクラ : 合図…！》
There's the signal!
また キミか…。
You again, huh...?
幾度か見た顔ね…。
九尾の子もいるみたいだし…。
I've seen that face often...
少し遊んであげましょうかね…。
(大蛇丸)サスケ君と
どっちが強くなってるか➡
みてあげるわ…！
(カブト)大蛇丸様は
これまでに三度転生している。
(カブト)第一の転生については 不明。
(カブト)
木ノ葉崩しの際に みせた姿が➡
２人目の器らしい。
本当は 写輪眼を持つ
うちは イタチの体が➡
欲しかったようだけど
入手に 失敗…。
(カブト)弟のサスケ君に狙いを変更し
四人衆と 君麻呂を使って➡
サスケ君を
引き入れようとしたのだが…。
(カブト)三代目との戦いで
両腕を封印されてしまった➡
大蛇丸様の肉体は
想像以上に早く限界を迎えた…。
(カブト)急を要すると判断したボクは➡
実験体たちを戦わせ➡
最後まで勝ち残った者を
器に選んだ。
それが現在の器 幻幽丸だ。
あれから すでに３年。
次の器も
順調に育っているようだし➡
楽しみだね…。
これは すべて ボクの独り言。
(カブト)気にしないでくれ…。
フフフ…。